(Howard:)Okay, calm down.
(Howard:)There's probably something
jammed behind it.
(Howard:)Just, uh, pull it out
and see what's there.
(Raj:)Hang on.
(Raj:)Oh... no. Oh, no.
Oh, God, no!
(Howard:)You know what, you sound busy--
I'm gonna let you go.
(Raj:)Dude, the whole front came off.
(Raj:)Now she's gonna know
I was snooping.
(Bernadette:)What's happening?
(Howard:)Raj was snooping through
Emily's drawers and broke one.
(Raj:)Aw.
(Bernadette:)I'm gonna miss her.
(Penny:)So what do you think?
(sighs)
(Leonard:)I thought it'd be
a little more... just more.
(Penny:)I'm not even sure
why we were out of breath.
Uh, I mean, d-did
we move at all?
(Leonard:)Maybe along the z-axis,
(Leonard:)but x and y are looking
pretty sad.
(Penny:)Okay, come on.
(Penny:)We are not old
boring people.